Brittney Wylie

britt.wylie13@gmail.com https://brittwylie.github.io/portfolio/

About Me

Hello! My name is Brittney but please call me Britt! I am an experienced web and multimedia developer skilled in responsive web design, graphic design, email development, and web accessibility. I am a passionate lifelong learner always open to new opportunities for personal and professional development.

Experience

Pier 1 Imports Web Production Specialist

Nov 2017 - Current

- Used HTML and CSS to build web promotions, and online editorials for Pier 1's Ecommerce and Marketing Departments.
- Built emails for Pier 1 using the inky email template, and created custom dynamic content using CSS and Responsys Personalization Language.
- Used Adobe Photoshop to slice, crop, and optimize images for use on Pier1.com and in Pier 1's marketing emails.
- Trained new team members on team standards and programs.

Southwest Airlines - HireGenics Culture Services Coordinator

June 2017 - Nov 2017

- Used online event management tool to build and test new web event sign ups and alter pre-existing ones.
- Edited photos in Photoshop to be printed and displayed.
- Created graphics in Illustrator to be printed and displayed at employee appreciation events.
 Southwest Airlines

Multimedia Developer Intern

January 2017 - May 2017

- Developed, designed and tested online training modules and job aids.
- Developed multimedia distance learning modules for training purposes in Storyline.
- Edited photos in Photoshop for use in online training.
- Designed custom graphics for use in online training in illustrator.

FedEx Office Center Consultant

March 2015 - December 2016

- Set up files for printing using Photoshop, Illustrator, and InDesign.
- Delivered printing and shipping solutions to customers.
- Assisted with training and onboarding of new team members.

Office Depot Copy and Print Specialist

December 2013- March 2015

- Designed custom business cards, flyers, and forms in Photoshop and Illustrator.
- Set up files for printing using Photoshop, Illustrator, and InDesign.
- Assisted with training and onboarding of new team members.

Education

University of Texas at Arlington

Bachelors of Arts in Communication Technology

Skills

- HTML5
- CSS3
- SCSS
- Knowledge of JavaScript
- Responsive Design
- Web accessibility
- Adobe Photoshop
- Adobe Illustrator
- Adobe Premier Pro
- Knowledge of Adobe After Effects
- Storyline
- Image Optimization
- Microsoft Office
- Project Management
- Problem Solving
- Communication
- Conflict Resolution
- Time Management
- Ability to work under pressure